I said, "Our group should not be in the pyramid of the idol world.
Ha-ha-ha!
A few idols won't turn their heads anymore!
Wow!Gold!
Gold!
You can't do this.
You can't do it?
Don't do it.
Oh, you?
It's still me, in case you were wondering.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're right.
Maybe all the idols should see this.
Hi, I'm Tokyo Denson. Please.
Come on. And please give my regards to Mr. Saccon.
Pleased to meet you.
Now, here they are again today. Go ahead.
Funny, funny, funny.
They're all funny.
If it's comedy you're after, we've got it.
Leave it to us.
Let's go!
Ruff Ruff.
Ruff ruff, please.Please.
So, in this issue.
For Rough Rough
The big event of the summer
This is a project just before the moodOh!
Congratulations!
How are you doing? Are you nervous?
Yes, three stages.
Thankfully, you've only just made your debut.
You've prepared me for this.
I have to make sure my performance is worthy of it.
I'm just trying to live up to it.
No, you're right.
It's nice to meet you.
I don't know.
I guess, from Mr. Saccon's point of view...
Mood is one of the most important
An important turning point.
I'm meeting someone for the first time.
I don't know much about it.
I don't know that much about it.
so today I'm going to ask someone who knows a lot about it.
So I thought
I'd like to introduce you to someone who knows a lot.Let's have them appear!
Please do.
Now, our special guest!
Misato Furukawa.
I'm Misato Furukawa.
Pleased to meet you.Amazing! So cute!
Idols with matching shoes are good idols.
It's important.
It's important
It's an idol with a pretty good budget.
That's what I think.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
It's true that this is the first time
It's the first time a comedian idol has come to our show.
I see.
Have you heard of Rachlaff?
Of course.
Yes, of course.
I'm sure you're a very powerful TV idol.
I've always thought of him as an idol.
I think.
You've been in the media a lot.
You are an idol, aren't you?You are an idol, aren't you?
I have a lot of opportunities to know the names of these idols.
I'm in the idol world.
Of course I know their names.
I know their names.
I'm in the idol world. I'm trying to turn them around.
He's so energetic!
Please take a look at this first.
Here you go.
It's amazing.
He's a torii (a gateway to the shrine).
You're also the headliner.
That's right.
People tend to think I'm great at torii.
But actually, I'm also a really good top batter.
Heh...
So it all starts with them.
It's a great honor to be the top batter.
You are going to be on the main stage again this year, right?
on the main stage this year, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm going to learn a lot from them.
This yearWe hope that this year's
I hope you will make the most of this year's TIFF stage
I'd like you to make the most of it for this year's TIFF stage.
But first...
What is this?
Well, it's a big event. Well, TIFF is a big event.
It's a big event and a lot of fun, but in my opinion
I think it is a place where you can measure the barometer of idol power.
Oh, I see. What do you mean by that?
First of all, there are separate stages.
Although they are not called "main stage" and "sub stage," you can tell which one is the main stage and which one is the sub stage.
But you can sort of understand it, can't you?
Ah, you know. This big stage. It would be great if we could do it there.
So, you can see how our group is in the pyramid of the idol world now.
Where do we stand in the pyramid of the idol world?
Where do we stand?
That's what I'm thinking about.
Yes, we do. Yes, there is.
Tis is a cruel thing,
No matter how many people come to the main stage,
it doesn't mean that the audience will come to see the show.
I see. I see.
That's really serious,
That's one of the most difficult things about TIFF,
The fans who come to see the show are idol nerds with a long history.The fans who are watching are already idol geeks of the past.
Ha. They've seen so many different people that their eyes are glazed over.
That's right. They won't be turned off by a few more idols.
Wow. That's a lot of work.
This year's TIFF has 220 groups.
It's amazing how you can shine there.
It's important.
I just put it on a high level.
Now, first of all, let's start with the patience here at TIFF.
Here we go.
1. TIFF is a battlefield, and you only need one person to increase the number of fans.
The day before is "Honyarara.
On the morning of the day of the event, you should be a fan of the event.
Well, No. 1.
All the idols are already there,
They are all coming with the mindset of "I'm going to get so many fans that I'm going to eat them up.
This is definitely a great opportunity for them,
But as I said before, we are getting fans from idol otaku who have been in the game for a long time,
I don't want to get 100 fans,
Just one is fine.
I see.
I'm just trying to get one more fan.
I've never seen such an active person with such power.
This is the first time for me.I'm new to this.
But why should it sting if I see it alone?
That's right.
By the way, from Mini's live performance.
This way.
It's true.
It's like you're all alone.
All alone in the battlefield.
That's amazing. That's great.
It's like you're delivering the message to that person.
By the way, the second thing.
I heard that this is a tip on preparation,
Do you know what's in here?
Yes, Nagamatsu.
Yes, Nagamatsu. Go to bed early the day before and get up early in the morning.
One of them is correct.
One is right, one is wrong.
Yes, Natsume.
Sleep early the day before, and swell up in the morning.
It's important.
Very important.
I'm doing lymphatic circulation here.
Everyone knows that.
That's important, but there is something more important.
Yes, Saito.Yes, Saito.
Go to bed early the day before, drink mackerel the morning of.
It's not that fashionable.
More. More important.
Yes, Hayashi.
Go to bed early the day before, eat white rice the morning of.
Oh! Correct.
Go to bed early the day before, and be sure to eat rice the morning of.
Yes. It's a matter of course,
In particular, my recommendation is to always eat a good breakfast.
It is important to eat well.
Tiffinan is very hot.
It's a game of physical strength.
If you get tired in the middle of the show, your performance will not go well,
And if you score a few points, you may not be able to speak well.
How do you like it, Mr. Sakuma?
No, it was almost like a battle.
It was really a battlefield.
The story of Sekihara.
It was literally a battlefield.
Then, let's talk about what to expect in the backyard.
Tiff's backyard is nothing but idols.
Oh, I see.
I think this is one of the points that fans look forward to there,
Taking two shots of idols and idols from other groups who don't usually take pictures,Idols and idols from other groups who don't usually take pictures of each other would take two shots of each other,
And then everyone posts them on Twitter.
I would like to see that kind of interaction.
That's right. And the fans see it,
They are happy to see this girl and this girl taking pictures of each other,
But there is one point to keep in mind.
Here it is.
Be consistent in your responses to other idols.
For example, let's say another idol asks you to take his/her picture.
You take a picture with their phone.
After that, it's time to decide.
It is a turning point whether or not to take a picture with your own phone.
Ah.
How about this? Which is better or worse? It's not good or bad.
Well, if you take a picture of your phone, then you are definitely going to put it on Twitter,
It's a kind of unspoken agreement.
It would be better to unify that.
It would be better to unify whether to take pictures or not.
It would be rude.
I hear that the girl has chosen an idol and is taking several photos of him or her,
It's like a reputation on the part of the idol.
I can't take a break from the backyard.
No, you see, I can't take a break in the backyard of TIFF.
It's for backyard use only.
I'm glad to hear this, really.I'm glad to hear this, really.
By the way, was there anyone that you thought was great when you saw him?
Sashihara-san.
He was chairman of TIFF for a while, wasn't he?
Everyone wants to have their picture taken with Sasshi.
Of course that is true.
They want to take pictures, but they don't have time to do so.
We don't even know when to go there.
We are all busy, aren't we?
Then, Sashihara-san took to Twitter,
To all the idols at TIFF, if you come to the backstage now, we can take your picture. Please come.
Wow.
That's really cool.
I'm just kidding.
This is really a story from Seki.
There was a time when I was in that position at another idol festival.
He said, "Remember Sashihara-san at that time. I wanted to do it.
I even went so far as to write a tweet.
No, I thought no one would line up.
Is that not true?
I quietly deleted the draft, didn't I?
Now, it's time for the last one.
The last one, "How to be on stage".
This is the most important part of the performance.This is the most important point for performance.
Now, here it is.
Don't let the sound break up.
And, #2, don't use "honyarara" when you are trying to get the audience excited.
First of all, don't interrupt the sound. What does this mean?
When the sound is going, the audience looks at you as if you are doing it.
But the moment the sound stops, they go to a different stage. They drift away.
As far as Tiffany is concerned, you should never introduce yourself.
You can't do it.
When you are in Tiffany, don't you do it?
We don't. We don't do it.
We don't do it.
They really asked me a few questions and said, "Let's get excited!
Wow.
Really.
That's right. If we have time for MC, we decided to add one more song.
Wow.
But I get the feeling that if I say my name, people will remember me.
Of course. Of course, it is better to say the name of the group "Rough Rough" as much as possible.
But there is a point to say it, too.
If you do it while the song is playing, the audience will be more likely to listen to it.
Oh, that's true.
So you say I shouldn't do funny, funny, funny.
Do you do it during the song?Do you want to do it during the song?
I like to do it during the song.
How long is it?
It's funny, it's funny, it's funny. We're all funny.
We can do comedy.
Leave it to us.
Ready.
I'm Ruff Ruff.
It's a bit long, isn't it?
Long.
It's a little long.
A little long.
Ah.
Ah, I'm learning a lot from this too.
As someone who has been doing this for 10 years, I can't say.
I think it's a point that people worry about when they are planning a festival,
I think it's the question of whether or not to bring new songs to festivals.
How about you guys? Do you have any?
If I were a guest, I would not want to bring my new songs to the festival.
Yes, that's right.
I want to hear the ones I'm used to hearing and the ones that have been perfected by everyone else.
When I go to festivals, I want to hear new songs.
Wow.
I'm not going to say that.You don't say.
Yes, I do.
But I heard that you shouldn't do that MC so much,
That's the first time I heard that.
That's a good point.
That's two points.
And the second one is.
When you encourage the audience, you shouldn't use 00.
Now, what goes in this 00?
Yes, Saito.
When you are encouraging customers, you should not say "you" or "you".
It's not very flattering.
Ah.
Or, you mean to agitate them.
Well, that's not what I meant.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, Hayashi.
When you are trying to agitate the customers, you shouldn't do that.
That's not what you mean. You mean that you tend to do it too much.
That's right. I often see that.
It's better not to do what you often see.
Now, Yoshimura.
When you encourage the audience, you shouldn't say, "Everybody, be cheerful.
What?
That's right. I think you shouldn't do that.Yes, it is. I don't think you should.
Surprisingly.
Yes, Natsume.
You shouldn't act like a pretty girl when you are encouraging the customers.
What do you mean?
Thank you! Like that.
You call me cute?
It's cute.
No, it's important.
Eh, I think it's good. I think it's good.
That's not what I meant.
Yes, Nagamatsu.
When you encourage the audience, you shouldn't say ordinary things like, "Let's get excited!
It's a bit mechanical. It's just a nuance.
Be specific.
Yes.
Yes, Suzuki.
You shouldn't use commands.
Are you talking out of your ass right now?
There's an empty reason.
You mean before you do something, anything.
I totally understand the feeling of wanting to do it during a song.
But for me personally, I think it's not good for idol live, or it's not my belief, or it's against my policy.
It's against my policy.
Yes, Hinata.Yes, sun.
When you agitate a customer, you should not use agitation as a connection, or a connection as a way to connect.
Ah, I see. The next step up is to take it to the next level.
We tend to do it, so we.
That's not what I meant.
Okay, Sasaki.
When you encourage the audience, you shouldn't encourage them during the dance part during the interlude or something.
Our live.
That's what we tend to do.
But I think you might be on the right track.
Yes, Saito.
When you encourage the audience, you call out the producer's name.
Isn't that just rapping rapping?
Takanishi.
You shouldn't use long sentences when you are trying to rouse the audience.
Ah, but that also relates to what you said earlier.
It's during the song.
The chorus.
This is during the chorus.
During the chorus.
Yes, Hayashi.
When you encourage the audience, you should stop singing.
Am I right?
Yes, correct.Yes, that is correct.
Yes, you are correct.
Amazing.
And when you're agitating a customer, yes, you should stop with the seh.
Ah.
I don't know, but I kind of get the image that this is more exciting.
Of course it's one of the very quickest ways to get people excited.
But from my point of view, I think it's better to sing properly.
Ah, as a policy.
I think it is important to present it as a show.
Yes.
I think all idols should see this.
Now, we are at the end, aren't we?
Yes, this is the last one.
This way.
This is the strongest stage witnessed by Furukawa Mirin.
Tiff.
Tiff, Tiff.
Yes, I have been performing at Tiff for many years now,
There is one moment that has left the greatest impression on me,
The first Tiff, Mr. Monochrome was on the stage,
I was the first batter at the first Tiff event.
The SE of the main stage came on and the members appeared on stage,
There was something they said at the beginning.
Oh, like a line.Oh, like the lines.
Yes, it is. That was the coolest.
Heh.
That's it.
Yamamoto-san said it?
Yes, Kanako-chan did.
What is it, Saito? You want to give it a try? Actually.
That's great.
So you'll win?
Win, yes.
What is your strongest first state, Mr. Yamamoto?
Wow, what's this?
Kanako?
It's always the same!
It always changes.
Isn't it?
Now, what is it?
Okay, I'll pull my finger out.
We're the best!
Mmm!
I'm kind of doing this.
Are you more of a fighter?
Which one?
Well, I'm pretty solid.Well, it's bishy.
Like one word says it all.
Okay, then, Natsune.
I feel like I'm really...
I feel like I really came out.
Good night.
I can shoot two shorts now!
Oh, good, good, good!
I said this mainly to Ayu.
If I said it for real...
By saying this, I've already
The fans are already feeling
Good morning!
Wow.
Yes, I'll take it.
Be cool!
The show's open!
Oh! Cool!
This is so cool!
This is cool!
Ew!
It's a little different.
It's really good.
It's more nuanced.
It's close in nuance!Nuances are close!
I think the Ryan game has started.
We're going to do it on M-1.
Let's do it on M-1.
Good direction.
Yes, Sasaki.
Oh!
Let's go!
Wow!
Any voices?
Let's go, or we'll go!
All right, then, Hayashi!
The pinnacle of the origin!
Oh! Cool! Cool!
Cool!
Now that's what I call a fucked-up head move.
Okay, well, Yoshimura!
Please!
Aim for your heart!
Amazing!
This is good!
This is so good!
First!
Top outerwear, at least.
Yes, second.Yes, the second one.
Top descent!
Oh!
Oh, game!
What do you think?
You're right!
I'd say so, right about now!
If I say so firmly, the complaints are here.
Gifu starts with us!
I can't say this.
Really, then, did you get to see it live?
I saw it live from the second floor.
The song goes "Boom, go, Kaito Shoujo! And then the music starts.
Wow!
How did you feel?
I really think that the MC's ability to charm people with just one word like that is very important.
I think it's very important to be able to charm people with just one word.
That's for sure.
That's right.
So, a few years later, there was a year when I was the top performer at a radio show.
It was 2015, wasn't it?
Was there?
And that's when I was taken by the cracks.
Oh! You did?
But there was a word, wasn't there?But there was a word, wasn't there?
Um, Gifu starts with us! Electric flame fashion!
Ha-ha-ha!
Born with a crack!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Do you have any goals for Tiffany Dell that you think all the members should have?
Yes, I do. I think we should do an ego-search right after the show.
Wow.
I've seen that kind of thing, and I'm kind of ego-seeking,
Oh, this song is really well received,
I can do EGOSA reflection on the spot,
It's like an on-the-spot Ego-Sa review meeting.
I thought it would be good to have such a meeting so that all the members could be united.
Well, we also stir things up in the middle of a song or something in Rough Rough Rough,
Are you excited? Are you able to speak up? Is it still going strong? I only have a repertoire of "Are you excited?
Hmmm....
I've already said "Let your voice out" so many times,
Ah....
Honestly, I'm not sure.
I have a theory that I want to show my live performance ability rather than just my voice,
Aaah.
I don't know if you all know this, but there are some troublesome customers,
I don't know if you all know this, but I have had some troublesome customers who have come to ruin the live show, or something,
A little bit nasty?
Yes, yes, yes.Yes, yes, yes.
I'm here to troll.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's kind of a good song, and it's kind of a great shout out or something,
I think that might happen in the future,
But in that kind of situation, my live ability was not enough,
I think that I gave birth to such a person.
I think that I have created such a person.
If your live show is really eye-catching, you can't behave in such a nasty way anymore,
I see. You just put on a show,
That's right.
It's enough to make you think there's no way you can get in, isn't it?
That's right. If you want to speak out after seeing my performance, you can do so,
Huh.
If you want to be quiet, you can just watch,
I think it's important for people to watch our show anyway.
Wow. This is important.
Okay, Yuka.
Yes.
Well, donations start with us.
Oh, my.
Say that last part.
I'm feeling a little...
One more word would be nothing,
Let's all say that we're willing to take on the PIF with that much feeling.Let's all say, with that much feeling, let's take on the PIF.
Let's say it.
Yes, let's say it.
Let's go.
Donations start with us.
All right.
Go for it.
Start with completion!
It was all really informative and I could remember it all.
Really, really now.
I thought I heard a lot of concrete things, as usual.
Indeed.
It was before skin, so there was a lot more I could do with skin.
That's for sure.
I'd like to try it when I'm all at the top.
Don't tell me.
Arisa says it at the beginning.
That's cool.
They'll all say it.
All of us will say it.
All of them will say it.
We'll all say it.I'll tell you all.
I say all of them.
Thank you for watching to the end.
Today is the crying version.
Sign up, please!
fingernail fried chicken
dancing girl
tonight
please!